fastsearch.net 2005-03-10

# Fast Search & Transfer - Home / Company / Privacy information

For questions about this privacy policy, please contact [helpdesk@fastsearch.com](mailto:helpdesk@fastsearch.com).

**Information Collection and Use**  
Fast Search & Transfer (FAST) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. FAST collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Registration**  
In order to download white papers or register for webinars, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used by FAST or by third parties acting on FAST’s behalf to contact users about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated information with our partners and vendors. We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders. If we do, this company will not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.   
If we partner with another party to provide specific services these parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter and Choice/Opt-out**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Users who have signed up to receive regular updates about our site and no longer wish to receive these updates may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [helpdesk@fastsearch.com](mailto:helpdesk@fastsearch.com).

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. Please email [helpdesk@fastsearch.com](mailto:helpdesk@fastsearch.com) if your information changes. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Security**  
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any such information transmitted to us over the Internet.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
